Of course there are many different washes to jeans and right now I have on something in the middle right.
It's kind of like a medium wash and it's faded at the top which I love because it matches everything.
It's a typical jean color.
Now you can have dark, you can have light, you can have medium.
Now Patricia over here has on gray jeans.
Now these are great because these go with a lot of sweaters I think.
You know you can do sweaters, you can do blazers like she has on right now.
And now gray is actually the new black.
Everybody is wearing gray lately.
And see now Patricia if you lift up your leg Patricia.
She rolled the bottom of her jeans.
What I'm going to have Patricia do is get her bottoms reattached so she doesn't have to roll them and then she'll have the original hem as well.
So she has the gray, I have the medium and then I'm going to show you the dark wash.
These are the dark wash. Now these are like the newest fad because everybody right now is wearing the dark jeans and these are called skinny jeans which I will model for you later.
We are not going to get into the skinny right now.
But the wash is what you need to look at because the dark goes with a lot of dark colors.
Now my favorite outfit is actually the dark wash with a white tank top and gold jewelry, that's my favorite outfit.
That's just like a hot outfit.
And you can pair it with Patricia's Brazilian boots.
So whether you go dark, light or medium there are fades for everybody, there are washes for everybody out there, just make sure you have a couple of different washes so you can mix up the shirts that go with them.